Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Records WAG.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: General Files, 1881-2013
  - Western Council: Committee Members, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Western Council: Dissolution and Re-Appointment, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Williams, Percy, 1978, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Wolfington, Iggie, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Series IV: Actors Work Program, 1986-1999
  - Advisory Board, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors: Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors: Meetings (includes audio tapes), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Budgets, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Actors’ Equity Association, 1989-1993, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, New York City Department of Aging, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Screen Actors’ Guild, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Counseling Department: Report, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Finances, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, undated, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hornet Foundation, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Individual Contributors, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New York City Department of Employment, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - New York City Department of Employment: Contractual Agreements, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - New York City Department of Employment: Project Operating Plan, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, 1989-2003 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Pilot Project: Reports, undated, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Regional Education Center, undated, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Regional Education Center: Educational Grants, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Regional Education Center: Finances, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Regional Education Center: Reports, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous, 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Willard Swire Scholarship Committee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Series V: Fundraising Activities, 1886-2002
  - Subseries V:A: Auctions and Bazaars, 1971-1989.
    - Auction, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Auction, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Auction: Correspondence from Donors (includes Katharine Hepburn, James Cagney, Emlyn Williams, Sidney Kingsley, George Cukor, Dorothy Stickney, Katherine Cornell, Judith Anderson, Cyril Ritchard, Anita Loos, and Zero Mostel), 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Auction: Moss Hart, “Once in a Lifetime” Manuscript, Authentication, etc., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Auction: Sponsors (includes correspondence from Nelson A. Rockefeller and Patricia Nixon), 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Auction, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Auction: "Going Once Twice Sold!" (Box 12, Folder 30A)
    - Auction: Howard Hawley Campaign, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Auction: NYPL Theatre Collection, Catalog, Oct 7, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Auction: Sotheby, Early American Furniture, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Bazaar, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Bazaar, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Bazaar, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Bazaar: Annie, Cast Christmas Party, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Bazaar: Anniversary, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Bazaar: Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Bazaar: Closing, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Bazaar Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Bazaar: Correspondence, 1975, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Bazaar: Donations and Gifts, undated, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Bazaar: Memorabilia: Peter Pan Collection, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Bazaar: Minskoff Theatre, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Bazaar: Springtime, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Bazaar: Springtime: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Bazaar West (Manhattan Plaza), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Subseries V:B: Benefits and Fairs, 1886-2002.
    - Benefit Program (Boston), 1886 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1892 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Benefit Program, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1907 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1910 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Program, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Program, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Benefit Program, Actors’ Fund Day, 1914 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Benefit Program, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Benefit Program, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Benefit Program, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Benefit Program: Fair, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Benefit Program, 1918 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Benefit Program, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Benefit Program, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Benefit Program (I), 1921 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Benefit Program (II), 1921 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Benefit Program, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Benefit Program, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Benefit Program, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Benefit Program, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Benefit Program, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Benefit Program: British Commission, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Program, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Benefit Program, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Benefit Program, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Program, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Benefit Program, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Benefit Program, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Benefit Program, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Benefit Program, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Benefit Program, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Program, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Benefit Program, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Benefit Program, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Special Performances: Benefit Programs (partial), 1944-1949 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Benefit Program, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Benefit Program, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Song of Norway, Jan 5, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Star Spangled Carnival, Hospitalized Veterans Music Service, Nov 29, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Benefit Program, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Special Performances: Benefit Programs (partial), 1951-1959 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Richard III, Mar 11, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Thurber Carnival, May 1, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Toys in the Attic, May 9, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Best Man, Jun 12, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, Jun 19, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - World of Suzie Wong, Aug 20, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - My Fair Lady, Aug 28, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Duel of Angels, Sep 25, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Taste of Honey, Nov 20, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Flower Drum Song, Nov 27, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Hostage, Nov 27, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - West Side Story, Nov 27, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - La Plume Da Ma Tante, Dec 11, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Evening with Mike Nichols and Elaine May, Dec 18, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - All the Way Home, Jan 1, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Five Finger Exercise, Jan 8, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Miracle Worker, Jan 8, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Period of Adjustment, Jan 15, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Advise and Consent, Jan 22, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Becket, Jan 29, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Invitation to a March, Feb 5, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Critics’ Choice, Feb 12, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Irma Le Douce, Feb 19, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Show Girl, Feb 26, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Unsinkable Molly Brown, Mar 5, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Wildcat, Mar 12, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree, Mar 19, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Rhinoceros, Mar 26, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Camelot, Apr 9, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Tenderloin, Apr 22, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Do Re Mi, Apr 30, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - American Dream, May 1, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Come Blow Your Horn, May 7, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Mary, Mary, May 14, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Devil’s Advocate, May 18, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Big Fish, Little Fish, May 21, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Golden Hind, May 21, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Far Country, Jun 4, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Happiest Girl in the World, Jun 11, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Majority of One, Jun 18, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Sound of Music, Jun 18, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Music Man, Aug 27, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Carnival, Oct 15, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, Oct 29, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Purlie Victorious, Nov 5, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Sound of Music, Nov 16, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Caretaker, Nov 19, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - From the Second City, Nov 26, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Andersonville Trial, Nov 27, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Evening with Yues Montand, Dec 3, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 10, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Milk and Honey, Dec 17, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fiorello, Jan 3, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sail Away, Jan 7, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Shot in the Dark, Jan 14, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Best Man, Jan 14, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Complaisant Lover, Jan 28, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Gay Life, Feb 4, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Gideon, Feb 11, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Man for All Seasons, Feb 18, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Write Me a Murder, Mar 4, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Night of the Iguana, Mar 11, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Take Her, She’s Mine, Mar 18, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Passage to India, Mar 25, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - No Strings, Apr 15, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - All American, May 20, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - I Can Get It for You Wholesale, May 29, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Subways Are for Sleeping, Jun 3, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Thousand Clowns, Jun 17, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Moon Is Blue, Jun 18, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Sep 23, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off, Nov 18, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Seidman and Son, Nov 25, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 2, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mary, Mary, Dec 2, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Beyond the Fringe, Dec 9, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Shot in the Dark, Dec 19, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Who’s Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, Jan 20, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Calculated Risk, Feb 3, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Never Too Late, Feb 10, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Lord Pengo, Feb 17, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Tchin-Tchin, Mar 3, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - School for Scandal, Mar 10, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Oliver!, Mar 17, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Come Blow Your Horn, Apr 1, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Little Me, Apr 7, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Ages of Man, Apr 14, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Photo Finish, May 12, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Jul 14, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree, Aug 4, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Enter Laughing, Sep 8, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - She Loves Me, Sep 22, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Man for All Seasons, Oct 27, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off, Nov 3, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Private Ear & the Public Eye, Nov 17, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying, Dec 8, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Case of Libel, Dec 15, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Camelot, Dec 29, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Jan 5, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Here’s Love, Jan 12, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Marathon, Jan 19, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ballad of the Sad Café, Jan 26, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Nobody Loves an Albatross, Feb 2, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Luther, Feb 9, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 110 in the Shade, Feb 16, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Girl Who Came to Supper, Feb 23, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Prime Minister, Mar 1, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dylan, Mar 8, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Any Wednesday, Apr 12, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Apr 16, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - What Makes Sammy Run?, Apr 19, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Funny Girl, May 3, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Who’s Afraid of Virginia Woolf, May 10, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hamlet, May 17, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - High Spirits, Jun 14, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - World of Kurt Weill in Song, Jun 28, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Subject Was Roses, Jul 19, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Fade Out- Fade In, Aug 9, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Baby Want a Kiss, Aug 16, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Three Sisters, Sep 20, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Oh What a Lovely War, Jan 3, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Owl and the Pussycat, Jan 17, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Luv, Jan 24, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Poor Richard, Jan 31, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Golden Boy, Feb 7, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Feb 14, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Committee, Feb 21, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Barefoot in the Park, Feb 28, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Mar 7, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - I Had a Ball, Mar 18, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Do I Hear a Waltz?, May 2, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Roar of the Greasepaint- the Smell of the Crowd, May 16, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Glass Menagerie, Jun 6, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Baker Street, May 23, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bernard Shaw Story, Aug 15, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Odd Couple, Sep 12, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Half a Sixpence, Sep 26, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Oct 17, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Chips with Everything, Nov 10, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Generation, Nov 28, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Funny Girl, Dec 19, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - You Can’t Take It with You, Jan 9, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - On a Clear Day You Can See Forever, Jan 30, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Zulu and the Zayda, Feb 13, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Skyscraper, Feb 20, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Hostile Witness, Mar 13, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Royal Hunt of the Sun, Mar 20, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Marat/De Sade, Mar 27, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Cactus Flower, Apr 3, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come, Apr 10, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Wait Until Dark, Apr 17, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Sweet Charity, Apr 24, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Wait a Minim!, May 8, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Dylan, May 9, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Impossible Years, May 22, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Odd Couple, Jul 17, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Show Boat, Aug 28, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Man of LaMancha, Sep 11, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Sep 25, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Mame, Oct 16, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Delicate Balance, May 27, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Apple Tree, Jan 15, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Cabaret, Jan 22, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Star Spangled Girl, Mar 5, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - At the Drop of Another Hat, Apr 9, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Homecoming, Apr 16, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Apr 23, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Black Comedy, Apr 30, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Mary, Mary, May 6, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - You Know I Can’t Hear You When the Water’s Running, May 21, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Don’t Drink the Water, Jun 4, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - South Pacific, Aug 27, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Man of LaMancha, Sep 10, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Mame, Oct 22, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Illy a Darling, Nov 5, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - I Do, I Do, Dec 3, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - There’s a Girl in My Soup, Dec 17, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Brief Lines, Jan 7, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Pantagleize, Jan 14, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - More Stately Mansions, Jan 21, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - How Now, Don Jones, Mar 10, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Happy Time, Mar 17, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead, Mar 24, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Mar 31, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, Apr 3, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Cabaret Cancelled Performance, Apr 7, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Price, May 5, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, May 12, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Plaza Suite, Jul 21, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - West Side Story, Aug 25, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - George M, Oct 13, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Lovers, Oct 27, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Marlene Dietrich, Nov 24, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Hair, Dec 7, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Show- Off, Dec 15, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Great White Hope, Jan 5, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Man in the Glass Bottom, Jan 19, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Celebration, Feb 23, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Zorba, Mar 9, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Hadrian VII, Mar 16, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Forty Carats, Mar 23, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Promises, Promises, Mar 30, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Play It Again, Sam, Apr 6, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Jimmy Shine, Apr 13, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Canterbury Tales, Apr 27, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Front Page, Jun 29, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Oklahoma!, Aug 24, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1776, Oct 5, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Butterflies Are Free, Jan 18, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hair, Feb 2, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, Mar 1, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Private Lives, Mar 15, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Canterbury Tales, Apr 5, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Hair, Apr 12, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Harvey, Apr 26, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Coco, May 7, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Applause, Sep 27, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Oct 18, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Company, Nov 8, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Conduct Unbecoming, Dec 6, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Two by Two, Jan 3, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Rothschilds, Jan 17, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Sleuth, Jan 24, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Home, Feb 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - No, No, Nanette, Mar 14, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Design for Living, Apr 18, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - School for Wives, Apr 25, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hair, May 17, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Follies, Oct 10, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Company, Oct 17, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, Jan 9, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Sleuth, Jan 23, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lenny, Jan 30, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Prisoner of Second Avenue, Feb 6, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Twigs, Feb 20, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, Mar 5, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Vivat! Vivat Regina!, Apr 9, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Purlie, Apr 23, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Sleuth, Apr 24, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Applause, Jun 11, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Follies, Jul 18, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Follies, Jul 21, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Follies, Jul 22, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - No, No, Nanette, Oct 3, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - That Championship Season, Nov 12, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Butley, Jan 14, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Grease, Feb 4, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Prisoner of Second Avenue, Feb 4, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Pippin, Mar 4, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Sunshine Boys, Mar 18, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Benefit Program: Auction, Apr 12, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Fishing Touches, Apr 15, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Changing Room, Apr 29, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Little Night Music, Jun 3, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Uncle Vanya, Jul 19, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Grease, Oct 28, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Bette Midler, Dec 23, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Liza, Jan 25, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Good Evening, Jan 27, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Good Doctor, Feb 10, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Moon for the Misbegotten, Mar 28, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Time for the Cuckoo, Apr 28, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Noel Coward in Two Keys, May 2, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Over Here, May 30, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Magic Show, Oct 27, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, Nov 24, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Gypsy, Dec 1, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Absurd Person Singular, Jan 12, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Sherlock Holmes, Jan 23, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Equus, Jun 26, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - In Praise of Love, Mar 2, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Doll’s House, Mar 23, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Boys from Syracuse, Apr 28, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Same Time Next Year, Jun 8, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Chorus Line, Nov 2, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Wiz, Dec 7, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Chicago, Feb 22, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Royal Family, Mar 7, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Very Good Eddie, Mar 21, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Equus, May 2, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Chorus Line, Aug 16, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - My Fair Lady, Aug 29, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - California Suite, Sep 12, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Wiz, Oct 17, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bubbling Brown Sugar, Oct 18, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Same Time, Next Year, Dec 26, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Guys and Dolls, Jan 2, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Waiting for Godot, Feb 28, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Chorus Line, Apr 17, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Annie, Sep 25, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Side by Side by Sondheim, Oct 23, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - King and I, Dec 18, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Dracula, Jan 8, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Gin Game, Jan 22, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Grease, Feb 20, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Touch of the Poet, Feb 26, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Chorus Line, Feb 26, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Hello, Dolly!, Mar 5, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Chapter Two, Mar 19, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Cold Storage, Mar 26, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Board of Advisors, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Clippings, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Clippings (II), Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Correspondence, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Night of 100 Stars, Playbill, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Quilt, Feb 14, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Reagan, Ronald, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 25)